<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PBHarmony</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="main_screen_intro">Welcome to PBHarmony! Are you looking for your PB and J soul-
        mate? Well look no further! Take the personality survey, and let PBHarmony make your PB and
        J match!</string>

    <string name="OldFashioned">Your soul-sandwich is the basic, yet delicious peanut butter and
        jelly. Simpler can be better in some cases, and you realize that. Sometimes, the old but
        tested ways of doing things can get the job done, and the standard PB and J is a prime
        example.
    </string>

    <string name="PBFruit">As someone who enjoys nature and being outdoors, or just being completely
        untamed, you like to bring your love of nature into many aspects of your life, including
        into your PB and J\'s. Take out the jelly, substitute it for fruit, and what you are left
        with is a wholesome sandwich with a freshness that can only come from the mother nature her
        self.
    </string>

    <string name="TheElvis">You know you are styling on a regular basis, and welcome the fact that
        all eyes are on you throughout the day. Let the world know you deserve all the attention by
        whipping up a grilled peanut butter, banana, and bacon sandwich, similar to the sandwich
        that Elvis so often enjoyed.
    </string>

    <string name="DeepFried">Thinking outside of the box is your specialty. You show your creative
        intuition when you come up with ways to improve anything and everything around you. What
        could be a more creative improvement to a PB and J than deep-frying it? Come to think of it,
        how many things in this world aren\'t improved upon when you fry them?
    </string>

    <string name="DoubleDecker">As the title of this sandwich suggests, you are livin\' large. You
        dwell in excess. It\'s how you live your life and you wouldn\'t choose any other way of
        living. Naturally, you are a perfect match for this super-sized rendition of the tasty PB
        and J.
    </string>

    <string name="PBJSriracha">It\'s safe to say that you are far from bland. You are one who wants
        socialize and make exciting things happen around you for own amusement. Your sandwich is
        involves an exciting twist to an all-time classics, which is the addition of arguably the
        highest-rated hot sauce in our day and age: Sriracha!
    </string>

    <string-array name="radio_button1">
        <item>You like Muscle Cars:OldFashioned</item>
        <item>You wear all the brand-name clothes:TheElvis</item>
        <item>You are a conversation-starter:PBJSriracha</item>
        <item>You are a fan of healthy foods:PBFruit</item>
        <item>You haven\'t showered in a month:PBFruit</item>
        <item>You are confident:TheElvis</item>
        <item>You desire to live in a high-rise/penthouse condo:DoubleDecker</item>
        <item>You are a dreamer:DeepFried</item>
        <item>You have tons of Bling:TheElvis</item>
        <item>You stockpile things that you like:DoubleDecker</item>
        <item>You appreciate tried-and-true methods of doing things:OldFashioned</item>
        <item>You feel uncomfortable when you are in a boring situation:PBJSriracha</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="radio_button2">
        <item>You find camping very enjoyable:PBFruit</item>
        <item>You are a collector:DoubleDecker</item>
        <item>You like classic music:OldFashioned</item>
        <item>You are an innovator:DeepFried</item>
        <item>You are outgoing/extroverted:PBJSriracha</item>
        <item>You like to fix things when they break:DeepFried</item>
        <item>You consider yourself a fan of nature:PBFruit</item>
        <item>You love being in the limelight:TheElvis</item>
        <item>You upgrade your fast-food meals to large:DoubleDecker</item>
        <item>You \"fake it \'til you make it\":TheElvis</item>
        <item>You try to add excitement to every moment:PBJSriracha</item>
        <item>You are a \"game-changer\":DeepFried</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="radio_button3">
        <item>You put hot sauce on everything:PBJSriracha</item>
        <item>You use a flip phone:OldFashioned</item>
        <item>You don\'t buy anything that isn\'t labeled \"all-natural\":PBFruit</item>
        <item>You \"strut your stuff\":TheElvis</item>
        <item>You always \"treat yo self\":DoubleDecker</item>
        <item>You decorate in vivid colors:PBJSriracha</item>
        <item>You always think about how things can be improved:DeepFried</item>
        <item>You prefer the nature trail to the mall:PBFruit</item>
        <item>You firmly believe \"it if ain\'t broke, don\'t fix it\":OldFashioned</item>
        <item>You have a very active mind:DeepFried</item>
        <item>You think that kids these days need to play outside more:OldFashioned</item>
        <item>You upgrade to new technology right when it comes out:DoubleDecker</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
